Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Episode 88
You vile dog!
Umur, Ivaz, you, your tribe, the troop
you want to establish...
...a rooted state, a mighty plane tree...
...I've heard all of these, Osman.
But you can't grow without light.
You will surrender to my darkness!
Who is under this mask?
We will see now.
Who are you?
You lived too long, Osman!
Too long!
But the time has come.
My Bey!
Master!
Come on, brother!
Barkın!
Don't let go of the demon!
Come on!
Who did this!
Who!
In the name of Allah!
Allah is the healer!
Akça!
Akça, bring the bowl!
Bring the bowl!
Allah is the healer!
Hang on, my Sheik, hang on!
The soup!
Akça Dervish!
Bring the soup!
Hang on, my Sheik, hang on!
Do you think it is the soup, Kumral Abdal?
The soup is poisoned!
What are you saying, Kumral Abdal?
My Sheik!
First Mari, Now my father.
Kumral Abdal...
...Cornelia?
We're in front of you, we're behind you.
You will die, Osman!
You will die!
Come to me, infidels!
Well done, Cerkutay!
Praise be!
-To you too, brother.
-Come on.
Come on.
Turan...
...go to the tribe.
Bring me Cornelia and Zehra.
Is something wrong?
Is Sheik fine?
Hurry, Turan!
I want them!
Osman!
If anything happens to my master...
...I will destroy Kayı upon your head!
You vile dog!
You killed Ivaz Bey!
You killed him!
What are you doing?
Malhun Hatun doesn't seem well.
She is ill, I guess.
She will be better when she gets some
rest, I hope.
Zehra Hatun, Sister Cornelia...
...Bala Hatun wants to see you
immediately.
What is it?
She said to come quickly.
That's all I know, Aygül Hatun.
My Bey!
You!
You made me lose that infidel!
I succumbed to my anger, my Bey.
He who can't control his anger
can't control anything!
You let that traitor breathe!
You...
Now...
...take the martyrs and Ivaz Bey
to the tribe.
Bury the martyrs at once!
Come on!
Yes, my Bey.
I will enter the tribe with martyrs,
again.
This same is enough for me.
My Bey.
It has Harmankaya Seal.
This is Kosses's arrow.
The union we formed obviously
broke the devil's game.
They attack from everywhere.
Söğüt
Death cup, wolfsbane...
...it looks like they mixed various
poisons.
My Sheik!
Bala, is my Sheik all right?
Cornelia.
The meal you brought poisoned my Sheik.
Hatuns!
How did this happen?
How did this happen, right, Cornelia?
Those you touch get poisoned.
First, Mari...
...now, my father.
I, I didn't do it.
How could I do such a thing?
How could you think this?
Would you say even if you did?
Those you breathe near get poisoned!
Who?
Who did this?
Who do you work for?
I didn't do it.
I didn't even touch the meal, Bala Hatun!
Then, was it you, Zehra?
Who else touched the soup?
I didn't do it.
I made the soup with Selcen Mother.
But I swear I didn't do such a thing.
You didn't, she didn't!
Who did?
Who did this to my father?
Bala Hatun!
We don't say it is you, sisters.
But the enemy is everywhere.
Zehra Hatun?
Cornelia?
Didn't you leave the soup ever?
No.
Zehra carried it all the way.
She didn't let anyone touch it.
Zehra...
...if you didn't then who did?
Get out!
Get out and think!
Think about who did this!
Get out!
Bala...
...you suspect Cornelia as well, right?
Is there anyone else to suspect, Aygül?
What about Mari?
Did she kill Mari too?
How?
Keep an eye on her, Aygül.
Follow where she goes, whom she sees.
We need to find who it is.
We will.
We will, Bala.
The evil clearly has entered the tribe,
Bala Hatun.
We must inform Osman Bey.
Don't worry.
We will find out who it is.
İnegöl Castle
Osman is up to something.
Where is Gündüz's grave, Nikola?
Did Kosses burn him?
Did you hear such a thing?
Kosses loves to show off.
He should have killed Gündüz and throw his
head in front of Osman already.
They just said he died.
All right.
Maybe Kosses took his revenge quietly.
Maybe Gündüz is alive.
And all of this is a game.
Osman, Master Arius.
Nothing about him surprises me.
But an enemy he can't see will drive him
to highly doubtç
I, Aya Nikola...
...swear on the Ceasar's name that...
...Osman will already be ruined before he
finds out who you are.
The darkness pays dearly for the service
rendered to it, Nkola.
Now the first thing we will do is
to clear Osman's doubts.
What do you have in mind, Master?
I will resurrect what I killed, Nikola.
I will give breath to Sheik Edebalı...
...whom I left breathless.
The owner of this arrow isn't Kosses.
Alps.
Mari Hatun's death...
...the slander thrown at Gündüz Bey...
...it is all to get Kosses and Turgut Bey
against us...
...and to eliminate my brother.
Their intention is to leave Kayı alone
and...
...stop the conquests!
Whoever did this...
...is the one who killed Ivaz Bey and
Umur Bey!
My Bey...
...did Gündüz Bey...
...die because of slander?
Gündüz Bey is alive.
He is now at the Kosses's castle.
Don't worry.
Thankfully!
So...
...my Bey...
...then who is doing all these?
Who is the traitor?
We will find out, Boran.
If you don't know where the trouble
comes from...
...you'll take a look at when it comes.
Barkın...
...and İbrahim Faki.
So, those two demons did all these?
Trouble began with their arrival.
We will act with doubt.
Başsungur.
My Bey?
You will be after Barkın.
Saltuk.
My Bey?
You will always watch İbrahim Faki.
Since they come from the darkness...
...you will be shadows.
Yes, my Bey.
Alps...
...you will be on alert.
They plant the seeds of discord...
...and spill our brothers' blood.
If it all comes down to you...
...then you won't believe what
you see and hear.
No one...
...will act without asking me.
Yes, my Bey!
We are going to Harmankaya.
Come on!
Both Turgut and Kosses.
We will cut off both of Osman's arms!
He will be alone.
But lone wolves are dangerous as well,
Nikola.
I'll pull out his teeth too.
He won't even be able to growl.
But first, he has to attack Kosses
with anger.
Kosses won't want to be harmed
and...
...will come to us.
Besides, Argus and my soldiers already
settled in Harmankaya.
We will not only turn Kosses and
Turgut against Osman but also...
...we will take them on our side.
Not yet.
First, I will wait for Osman to make
a move against Kosses.
I will wait for news from my spy.
Soldier.
Excuse me.
Precaution.
The gold you wanted, Master Arius.
But you didn't tell me what you wanted
it for.
To drown the Turks in the palm of
darkness, Nikola.
This gold will go to Barkın.
Barkın, who will be the bey of
Kızılbey Oğulları.
Barkın is with Osman but he is one of us.
Most brutal warrior of the darkness.
A knight to tear the Turks to pieces.
This gold will be one of his most powerful
weapons for this cause.
Harmankaya Castle.
You! Where are you going?
Stop!
Go on.
Come on, Osman Bey.
Thank you, Samuel.
I will go now.
Here you go.
Here he is.
Ivaz Bey is dead...
...Kosses.
This arrow is ours.
Where did you find it?
It fell in front of me as I took off
the mask...
... from the devil's face.
They want to get their job done.
First, they turned you against us...
...now they want to turn Kosses
against you.
You are right, Turgut Bey.
Who attacked you?
Isn't there any other trace?
Whoever killed Mari attacked.
Whoever burned the Söğüt attacked.
Whoever killed Ivaz Bey...
...attacked.
But now I am after those I suspect.
Where is my brother?
Samuel.
Kosses.
It's only natural for me to tie the hands
of someone I think...
...is responsible for my brother's death,
Osman Bey.
Brother.
You will continue to seem dead.
You won't come to the tribe for a while.
We agree until the truth comes out,
my Bey.
What will we do now, Osman Bey?
Now, it is your turn, Turgut Bey.
Kosses proved he is against me by killing
my brother and attacking me.
You will be against me too.
They'll think we're at each other's
throats with our swords.
We do whatever it takes.
What it takes is the conquest.
They set all the traps to stop
the conquest.
We won't stop so that we be victorious.
Of course, don't worry.
So, how do we do this?
Thanks to you and Turgut Bey.
The Lord of Inhisar is Nikola's ally.
Only support force coming from the east
will be from there.
Inhisar is important.
We will take it first.
Without any battle preparations.
Later we will arrive at Inegöl's doors.
Couldn't you find it yet, Kumral Abdal?
The antidote I gave doesn't help.
My Sheik will die in my hands.
My Allah, protect him!
My Allah, who gave the cure to
Prophet Eyüp...
...help us.
Don't leave us in the dark.
-Show us the way.
-Amen.
May peace be with you.
-May peace be with you.
Bala Hatun, Akça Dervish told me.
How is he?
Who would want to hurt, Sheik Edebalı?
We don't know, İbrahim Faki.
Let my Sheik get rid of the claws of
this poison...
... then the time will come
for reckoning.
It's like they mixed all kinds of poisons
and put them in, İbrahim Faki.
The antidote doesn't work.
I don't know what to do.
I am here, Kumral Abdal!
I found what you asked for.
What is that?
Ground hele.
It may work.
I hope the healing from them.
Do you know what he was poisoned with?
We don't know who did it and how but...
...the food was poisoned.
It is as you said, Kumral Abdal.
This is really strong.
I know a poison like this but...
...there is no one here who may know it.
I've seen it used a lot in the east.
It killed those it poisoned in one night.
Heaven forbid, İbrahim Faki!
Isn't there a cure?
We will find one, I hope.
Kumral Abdal, you did your best.
Let me try this time.
You neither could protect my father...
...nor my uncle.
Is this how you keep your promise, Barkın?
Don't, my Selvi.
Don't.
Don't hurt me even more.
My heart burns, Barkın.
I have no one left.
My father is gone, Barkın!
You have me, Selvi.
Am I not your family?
What did I do wrong?
Why did Ivaz Bey and Uğur Bey set off?
Because of Osman.
He couldn't protect them.
Osman is one who could not clean
his lands from the enemies.
Are we guilty for it?
My Selvi...
...Osman could not recognize
his traitor brother.
Why am I guilty for it?
Why did we come here, Barkın?
For all this pain?
My Selvi...
...there is no turning back now.
When the day comes, I will take revenge
on Osman...
...who caused your father's death...
...and on those who killed your father.
Promise me, Barkın.
You will avenge both my father and
my uncle!
I promise, Selvi.
I won't die before I take their revenge.
But...
...I won't leave Ivaz Bey's tribe
without a leader.
Your father's will was for me to the Bey.
I will be.
Even the Kızılbey Oğulları will see
the truth at the assembly.
Come here, my Selvi.
I want to marry you after the assembly.
What are you saying, Barkın?
I just buried my father! What marriage
are you talking about?
Your father would want this as well,
my Selvi.
The Beys won't take me seriously until
our wedding is done.
Now we will get married.
It is my duty to Ivaz Bey to make
a wedding worthy of us...
...after our mourning is over.
He is opening his eyes! Thankfully!
Father! Father!
Praise be!
Thank you, my Allah!
My Sheik?
Get better soon, my Sheik.
Thank you, İbrahim Faki.
You are a savior!
A savior!
How can I ever repay you...
...now that you healed my Sheik?
Our home is now your home, İbrahim Faki.
We owe you a life.
Don't mention it. It is nothing.
I will go to the tavern now. I will visit
you later, I hope.
Zehra. Cornelia.
Head to the tribe.
You go.
I'll stay with Bala Hatun.
My bey, I'm watching Barkın.
He received two chests of
gold today.
From whom?
I don't know, my bey.
Someone must've left it earlier.
Whoever pays him the coins
receives his service.
-Keep your eyes on him.
-As you order.
He who creates
by just saying...
who fills our heart with
the goodness of faith...
great Allah's ninety-nine names!
With the name of Allah!
Umur Bey and İhvaz Bey.
They were riding to these borders
to help us.
They killed them.
Barkın Bey...
said that Mongols killed Umur Bey.
And when we reached İhvaz Bey...
we found Kosses' arrows.
My bey. We took Kosses to our tribe.
We should've expected it from the heathen.
Kosses, Nikola; we worked with one heathen
to beat the other.
The attack at Söğüt. Do we know
who did it?
Don't worry.
We will find it.
Those who attack us without
honor will surely pay.
You will, Osman Bey?
You couldn't make the murderer of my
wife and baby pay.
If Kosses, who you see as an enemy
now didn't kill him...
justice wouldn't be served.
Turgut.
You are in the bey's tent.
Know your words and position.
You couldn't protect, Osman Bey.
Is it a lie?
You couldn't protect.
The beys who follow you get
hunted down one by one.
Umur Bey.
İhvaz Bey.
They were all warriors.
You couldn't protect Söğüt either.
Even Sheik Edebali is
facing death.
Now, after losing the lives,
your settling scores don't matter.
Are you afraid that the people
who are close to me are hunted?
One who is afraid to be a prey
can't become a hunter.
I was silent because
you were in pain.
But...
get out of my face now!
Get out!
Alright.
Am I allowed, Osman bey?
İhvaz Bey...
Umur Bey...
we all share that pain.
But...
my heart is burning
the most for them.
They are attacking from
all sides.
Osman Bey is on the righteous
path.
Beys, the point is...
the three that bears fruit will
be stoned.
Thank you.
Alps.
Turgut Bey will never come to this tribe.
If he comes near...
you will drive him away.
He has no value in my eyes now.
As you order, my bey.
The council is over.
Come on.
I can't understand it, Cornelia?
How did this happen?
I don't know, Zehra.
I don't know.
Let's stop by the marketplace.
I'll wait by the horses. You take care
of your business and come.
Alright.
Forgive me. I'm checking if İbrahim
Fakıh is inside.
He left before me.
Didn't you see?
I went to the marketplace.
He must have left then.
-Thank you.
-Thank you, too.
I don't have much time.
Zehra is waiting.
Why did you save him, sir?
You said that we would kill him.
You said that the light
of the Oghuz would fade.
Pretty Cornelia.
Kumral noticed the poison. It was a
matter of time to find the antidote.
We couldn't make that fool a hero.
If someone will profit from
this chaos...
it should always be us.
And saving Edebali is the best way
to gain their trust.
Right.
They'll trust you more now.
Everything is for our holy cause.
You will get close into
the hearts of them.
Don't worry.
I'm working on it.
But...
But?
Bala is suspicious of me.
This last move took all the
attentions to me.
Then, Beautiful Cornelia.
It's time for our next move.
But...
this will be painful.
Saltuk. What are you doing here?
I'm following İbrahim Fakih
by my bey's orders.
But I lost his track.
Have you seen him, Aygül Hatun?
He left the lodge.
I hope it's good.
Now, we have a clue
on our suspicions.
Alps...
are following the master and
Barkın.
But during this time, we won't
be staying idle here.
Konur.
Speak.
Speak so that everyone
will hear it.
İnhisar's lord valued
his life, my bey.
Firstly...
I told him that we surrounded
the castle.
Then, I gave him our conditions.
From now...
we'll feed our animals on
their grass.
No soldier will question the
ones who carry Kayı flag.
In return for keeping his castle...
they'll pay with two chests of gold
as a tribute.
Mashallah.
But tell me this.
Did he accept all this voluntarily?
What if someone opposes to this
agreement?
When they say that they'll protect
him from Osman...
will he accept it?
Whoever it is that will protect
him from Osman...
he'll jump right into it.
Good.
Now, our fake hostility with
Turgut Bey should be heard.
Then, our enemies will go to
Kosses and Turgut Bey.
When they sit at the table
as allies...
we'll take İnhisar on that table.
Inshallah.
Thank Allah, my bey.
It's time for conquest, my bey.
Indeed.
Our fresh weapons are waiting
to spell heathen blood, my bey.
Thank you, Master Davud.
May I enter, my bey?
Come in.
My bey. Bala Hatun sent news.
Sheik Edebali is poisoned.
As you wanted. Malhun won't
wake up until you become the bey.
Cornelia.
You are really venomous.
-How did you do it?
-I added some herbs to her water.
Oh, my pretty girl.
You don't have fever either.
What happened to you?
I don't know, mother.
I can't stand up.
I can't even open my eyes.
Did she eat what I brought?
She did, mother Selcan.
Rest. I'll come again, my girl.
Alright, mother.
Stay with her.
Malhun Hatun.
Alaca.
Thank you, my girl.
Mother.
How is Malhun?
She barely ate now.
But she hardly opens her eyes.
Inshallah, she'll get up tomorrow.
Inshallah.
Sit.
It's good to be cautious, mother.
The enemy is close to us.
True, my girl.
We'll find them.
Thank you, my girl.
Cornelia.
Come and sit, my girl.
Zehra will do it.
Take a seat.
Sit.
Thank you.
With the name of Allah.
Come on.
Söğüt
Behold, my sheik!
The fake life...
With the name of Allah.
Salam Alaikum.
Alaikum Salam.
My sheik.
May Allah always keep you
with us.
Thank Allah, we are destined
to talk to you again.
We are thankful to what
Allah gives us.
Come on.
With the name of Allah.
Thank Allah for giving you
back to us.
Thank you, Kumral Abdal.
Inshallah, we'll sacrifice our
desires to Allah's way.
And we'll be one of the
saved ones.
Inshallah.
How can we sacrifice our desires
for Allah's way?
By standing away from the enemy, Akça.
Will the enemies come to an
end in these lands, my sheik?
A valiant has many enemies.
Strong ones.
A Muslim's greatest enemy is the devil.
So, how much do we know
our enemy?
He knows us very well.
If we are a scholar, he makes us
brag about our science.
If we are beautiful...
our beauty flounder to
show itself.
If we are rich, he makes us stingy.
If we aren't, he makes us cruel.
If we are students, he makes us lazy.
And how much do we know him?
How can we stay away from
his tricks?
How can we destroy his might?
To make the devil kneel and
destroy him...
firstly, we will be good Muslims.
Now, you say that...
how will we be good Muslims?
Our prophet says that...
Peace be upon his name.
A person who sees Allah
as the god...
Islam as the religion...
Muhammad as the prophet...
has tasted the taste of faith.
If we get the flavour of faith...
then, we make the devil kneel.
The one who tastes the flavour
of faith...
will make Islam his priority.
Islam is more important than
his position.
More important than the spouse,
children...
lover.
Nothing in the world can keep him away
from the salaat.
He won't forget to give alms.
He won't be prideful for
sitting on a throne.
If there are scholars who are
real Muslims in a country...
science rears up there.
If there are real judges...
the country has justice too.
If there are real merchants...
that country prospers.
We all mirror each other.
What did our ancestors say?
A rotten apple spoils the barrel.
Allah's words say...
Allah has didn't create two hearts
in one person's chest.
If there aren't two hearts in one chest,
one Muslim shouldn't carry two loves.
He shouldn't say that he is a Muslim
and commit adultery.
He should protect the goods trusted
by the other.
He should perform the salaat
rightly.
He should give his alms.
I hear it. Some people
neglect their salaat.
Some people open their stores
without performing the morning salaat.
My heart is burning.
What kind of a Muslim am I that
my word doesn't work on you?
I'm devastated.
My dear ones.
My Allah says...
Who can speak better than the man who
calls people to the way of Allah?
I am a Muslim.
Then, may Allah destine us to become
real Muslims.
Amin.
Amin. Amin, my sheik.
I'm tired.
I'm hungry.
A child.
Did you forget your tent, child?
And he is eating!
If Aygül Hatun sees you, even I can't
save you.
I hope you left some for me.
He is sharing his bread with me!
Are you hungry?
Where are your parents?
Who am I talking to?
Did you gulp down your tongue?
Slowly, slowly.
Slowly.
Open your mouth.
Come on, it's coming!
The basmala first!
With Allah's name!
Good job!
This one. This one.
We'll eat it.
The horsemen are coming.
Mashallah to my warrior!
Mashallah!
We'll use our spoons. Right hand,
right hand. Eat with your right hand.
Mashallah.
Mashallah to my warrior.
Aygül Hatun. This warrior
lost his tent.
He wanted to come to us.
But he doesn't speak.
Just laugh.
Why are you crying, mad girl?
Nothing.
Mother!
Kayı. Cerkutay.
Kayı?
Baby Kayı?
Mashallah to my warrior!
You are a man now, Kayı!
Welcome, Kayı!
Welcome, Kayı.
İnegöl Castle
Michael Kosses.
Aya Nikola.
My dear friend.
It's been a really long time.
It has, Nikola.
It has.
I wish it wasn't for something
like this.
What is that, Nikola?
Osman.
If the lord of İnhisar stood with us
and helped against Osman...
maybe this wouldn't
happen today.
Of course.
I mean...
you shouldn't be waiting for the
fire...
to spread to your house.
Anyway.
So, my friend.
What can we do for you?
Osman.
He sent his man to my castle.
He forced me into an agreement.
You are like a vessel that has
the wind on its sails.
I'll be the rock that will sink you.
I need your help to
stand against Osman.
Right away.
I'll give my best soldiers to
you.
I see that Osman won't stop, Nikola.
Maybe if we don't unite now...
no wall will stop him.
Osman will break the treaty...
and march to İnhisar first.
Then, to İnegöl.
Tomorrow, we'll be at the castle
with Nikola.
And of course, Turgut will be with
us.
Turgut?
I don't want a Turk in my castle, Kosses.
If we got rid of Geyhatu and the Vizier
thanks to Osman...
we can get rid of Osman thanks to Turgut.
Trust us.
This is how the Turks work.
Use it and throw it.
That's what we'll do.
We'll use them and
throw them away.
Alright.
But it's your responsibility.
I'll be waiting.
I'm grateful.
Lord Matheus.
For revenge, Kosses, huh?
You are after new alliances for revenge.
What can I do?
This is how revenge is.
The revenge that made me Osman's
friend to destroy you...
now making me Turgut's friend
to destroy Osman.
My girl, are you alright?
Cornelia?
Cornelia, are you alright?
She is poisoned! Mother, she is poisoned!
Zehra!
Zehra?
My girl.
Help me here.
Puke it.
Come on, my girl.
No.
O' passanger!
Where are you heading?
To the Kızıl Elma!
Have you seen Kosses' excitement, master?
He was so eager to give soldiers
against Osman.
You won't join Kosses' invitation, Nikola.
Sure. But why?
You are like a leave hanging
on the air.
You follow the stream.
Kosses was with Osman until yesterday.
He can't gain my trust that easily.
As you want, master.
Don't forget this, Nikola.
If the Turks don't have trouble,
they become the trouble.
We are here to be their trouble.
Yes, master.
What's our next move?
Barkın.
Barkın must take the tribes.
Then, I'll take Osman's breath.
I won't let him dream of conquests.
Nikola asked for soldiers near Yenişehir
from the emperor.
He is talking about the soldiers
Sultan Mesud will send.
He wants to equalize the situtation.
What else?
And he demanded help against
a Turkish siege.
Oil, mostly.
Weasel.
The helps to go to Nikola will
take this way.
Cutting the supply will break
İnegöl's strenght.
Tell me about Bursa.
Bursa that you want to make
the capital of your country.
The walls are hard to pass.
Even stopping the supply line
will take years.
Many villages are supporting it.
The riches of it might be equal to
a hundred, maybe a thousand Söğüt.
That's why we want it.
It'll become our home.
But, there is time.
When we take İnhisar...
we'll cut all the supplies coming
from the east.
The rest is being cautious against
the ones coming from the west.
If your relative, emperor Andrenikos
heard this...
If my relative, emperor Andrenikos...
heard the information you
bring to us?
Artholos.
We know that İnhisar isn't enough
to conquer İnegöl.
But the important part, who'll fill
Rogatus' place?
The new lord of Bilecik, whose
side will he be on?
There are some names rumored.
I'll inform Osman Bey when it's
certain.
You'll bring the information.
I'll bring the soldiers.
All the alps.
Kosses and Turgut Bey will stand with me.
First, İnhisar...
İnegöl...
Bilecik.
İznik.
And...
Bursa.
Children will be raised.
Causes will grow.
This nation that is loyal to a dream,
the idea of world order...
will conquest Constantinople
one day...
and make it home.
Alright.
All people deserve prosperity and peace.
The most importantly...
these lands will live in peace.
These lands will be ruled with
justice.
Intelligence is crucial in winning
a war.
And you keep the key, Osman Bey.
The key to conquest is the heart.
The rest is just tools.
They think that they divided us.
Finished us.
But...
thank Allah.
We haven't started yet.
Now, it's time for conquest.
Allahu Akbar.
Alright.
Bring water.
Alaca, go to the infirmary and
bring what I said.
Come on!
Come on, my girl.
Alps!
Take Zehra to the prisoner tent!
And inform Kumral Abdal.
Bala Hatun.
Bala Hatun! I didn't do it!
I didn't do it!
I didn't hurt anyone.
Bala Hatun! Bala Hatun!
What kind of a tribe is this?
The troubles and traitors
never end!
Selda Hatun, know your words.
We came for condolences.
Is it a bad time?
You are just in time, İbrahim Fakih.
Cornelia is poisoned now!
It's the same with Sheik Edebali's
poison.
Beys.
I know.
You are asking why we are here.
It's important matter.
Walls have ears in Kayı Tribe.
As the Kızılbeyoğlu Tribe,
we've been with Osman Bey.
It's Umur Bey's will.
So, say it now.
Umur Bey and İhvaz Bey both died
on their way to Osman Bey.
I'm here by their will and wish.
Tell me.
Why were they on the way?
For the future of the Turks.
To reach the Kızıl Elma.
Now, I ask you.
One who can't keep his own
roads safe...
how can he open the way
to the Kızıl Elma?
Barkın Bey. You were with Umur Bey
when he died.
Will the man who can't protect his bey
will be our bey?
You are right?
I couldn't protect them.
And I couldn't die.
But...
Allah is my witness that...
I didn't step back from a fight...
or turn my back.
I fought bravely and couldn't protect him.
And it's my shame.
We have many martyrs!
Are you questioning everyone
who survives?
Continue, Barkın Bey.
Söğüt is the heart of the Kayı.
He can't even protect it.
We came here to protect
the borders...
to run for one battle
after another.
We won't bow down to Osman Bey
just because our beys are gone.
If we need a bey...
it can be me.
I'm poor.
But...
my tribe will prosper.
May Allah bless you, İbrahim Fakih.
Thank Allah.
She breaths again.
Give this to her.
Allah is the one healing.
We are just tools.
Mashallah. You understand it
with a single look.
You are pretty informed on this.
Science is knowing the nature.
Poison is a part of it.
We are educated on it too.
Thank Allah.
Firstly, my sheik...
now Cornelia.
How will we pay our debt?
Stay in our tribe today.
Don't travel.
Osman Bey will come too.
He'll want to see you.
İbrahim Fakih.
Osman Bey.
I owed you a life.
Now it's two.
Come to my tent for dinner.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
But it was a tiring day.
Forgive me for tonight.
Cornelia is the last to see Mari.
She brought the food to the lodge
We suspected her.
But Cornelia is poisoned now, my bey.
The traitor was one of us.
Zehra has no one.
Who would make her do this?
We'll make her speak.
What do you think, mother?
Until now, I always suspected
Cornelia, son.
But now I'm sure.
It was Cornelia.
She told Bala that she didn't
touch the meal.
But she put the meal on the bowl.
Oh, my Ayşe.
And she got the meal
from Ayşe.
When she realized that Bala suspected
her, she poisoned herself.
Do you say that she risked death?
She struggled in front of our eyes.
She would.
And again, İbrahim Fakih came.
Every time we are in trouble...
İbrahim Fakih comes in time
Oh, my son.
Oh...
Have you seen it?
Your brother is innocent.
My children died for nothing.
Mother.
I couldn't tell you.
Forgive me.
What?
Gündüz Bey and Ayşe Hatun
are safe and sound.
Thank Allah!
No one will hear it.
The enemies attack from the shadows.
We'll fight them secretly.
Only the alps and you.
Bala, we need the one
who holds the leashes.
But still question Zehra Hatun.
Don't worry, my bey.
May I enter, my bey?
Come, Cerkutay.
Oh, my nephew is here!
Come here, my lion!
Come here!
Kayı Alp!
You are a soldier!
Mashallah to you!
Mashallah!
My lion.
He would grow bigger if
had sleept.
What did I tell you, Cerkutay?
He should sleep.
Why didn't he sleep?
He didn't, mad girl!
He didn't!
He burned the tent by
shouting 'mother'!
Mashallah to my valiant.
Did you shout 'mother', Kayı?
Coins don't work on them.
Poverty doesn't disband them.
Why did we give the coins, then?
Barkın.
We did it to show off.
This was the show off of a bey
who doesn't care about money.
It shows that you will never be
arrogant.
You will give promises, Barkın.
You will give them a dream.
They will sleep and wake up
with that dream.
They like peace.
They like unity.
But they know that it's all possible
through destroying the heathens.
For that, Barkın...
you will promise them raids.
Raids.
That's our weakness.
You'll hit them on their
weak points.
It seems like Barkın is busy.
What are they talking about?
We don't know their deal but...
we keep our eyes on them.
We'll find out.
Alps!
This road leads to İnhisar.
But the other side of the walls doesn't
only contain İnhisar!
Behind those walls, there is İnegöl!
Yesterday, we had Geyhatu and
Alemşah...
tomorrow we have other enemies.
It seems that...
as long as we don't become
a state...
they'll try to stop us.
Now, it's time.
It's time for conquests!
Allahu Akbar!
Ya Allah!
Barkın Bey.
You are here.
Selvi Hatun is here.
Where is Umur Bey's daughter,
Malhun Hatun?
Malhun Hatun is resting.
If she felt well...
she would be among us.
Will we elect Umur Bey's
tribe's head without his daughter?
His brother İhvaz Bey's daughter
is here.
Isn't it enough?
Now.
I want to be the bey
of the both tribes.
I see that there is no one else
who wants it.
So, to honor our laws, we
are gathering a council here.
He isn't facing you.
He is busy with more
important things.
But you have competitors, Barkın Bey.
Speak.
Who is it?
Osman Bey!
Malhun Hatun is Osman Bey's wife.
Umur Bey left her to us.
So, we want to follow Osman Bey.
And these are your coins.
Come on.
Hasan Bey!
Are you afraid of me?
I'm not, Barkın Bey!
Yes.
But...
you are afraid of Osman Bey.
You are afraid of facing him.
One who cares about his tribe
wouldn't follow another!
I rode my horse for
the safety of the borders.
I joined battles!
I lost my alps.
Hasan Bey!
I didn't give the coins to you
that you can reject them.
I gave them to the poor in your
tribe to be happy.
It's obvious that you don't
care about your people.
Now, I ask you.
Beys.
Do you want Osman Bey, who is incapable
of protecting his own, as your leader?
Or Barkın Bey who risks his own life
for your safety?
Tell me.
We vote for Barkın Bey.
I also vote for Barkın Bey.
Hasan Bey, İhvaz Bey chose Barkın
Bey to be his son-in-law.
He saw the truth.
I vote for Barkın Bey.
Thank you.
İnhisar Castle
I'm sorry for your sister, Lod Kosses.
But she prepared her end by
marrying a Turk.
I took my sister's revenge.
Lord Matheus.
I sent Osman's brother to hell.
But if you say such a thing again...
you will go and see him there.
Alright. Are you feeling peaceful now?
To feel peaceful, I need to kill
all those Turks, Matheus.
Don't worry.
I know how to do that.
Turgut will join us soon.
He wants to take revenge too.
Don't say such things with him.
Allow me to choose my own words
in my own castle.
Just as I choose my own alliances.
Isn't this a lot of soldiers, Matheus?
Why?
I'm hosting a Turk.
This is little.
Sir, they are coming.
I congratulate your beyhood, Barkın bey.
I hope it will be good.
Inshallah.
Soon, we'll host a festival.
If we are chosen the bey...
it's not to oppose Osman Bey
but to support him.
After we survive
these troubles...
we'll host our festival too.
Thank you.
Here is Turgut Bey, Lord Matheus.
You are the first Turk to eat
in my castle.
Inshallah, many more will eat in
your castle.
I'm talking about friendship.
Will he sit with us?
That's my brother.
He will stand behind me!
Of course.
If it's not a trouble for you, Matheus.
As long as he is standing and
stays away from me.
Let's get to the table.
Lord Kosses' soldiers.
You are late.
We followed Lord Kosses' orders.
Wait here.
Nikola should be here soon.
Nikola isn't usually late.
Let's wait for a little
longer.
The help we expect from the emperor
will come this way.
Soldiers, Argus.
Did the soldiers go to
guard them?
Yes, sir.
Our soldiers are providing
their security.
Good.
Good, Argus.
Our oil is coming.
Our walls are getting stronger.
But most importantly...
we have enough supplies for
years.
But, will it be enough?
No.
The best defense...
is offense.
What is our target, sir?
Prepare the soldiers.
We are charging.
Yes, sir.
Did you witness it?
We have.
May Allah make it good.
My Allah...
We witnessed the treaty of these
children of ours.
You witness it too.
May Allah bless this union.
Amin.
Give them prosperity, love, and peace
in their marriage.
-Amin.
Don't give them any discord, hate,
seperation.
Amin.
Lord Kosses.
You will protect me against Osman,
won't you?
Lord Matheus.
I think you are overestimating Osman.
Kosses is right. Osman is rotting
his life after a dream.
For our friendship and unity.
If we are friends.
Let me give you some advice.
If you want to beat your enemy.
You should get to know him.
Tell me about Osman's
dream, then.
Let me tell you.
Osman wants to stop all the tyrants,
all over the world.
For this reason, he wants to
control the world.
What a dream.
Are you one of the tyrants?
Your people don't like you.
You oppress them with
heavy taxes.
My people, my rules.
It's not your concern, Turgut Bey.
Because you think like that...
it concerns Osman Bey.
Salam Alaikum.
Magneficus!
Traitors! You took Osman
to my castle.
But you were too naive, Matheus.
We heard it, Matheus.
You ruled as a tyrant.
But we came here with the
sword of justice.
Now, İnhisar belongs to the Kayı,
to the Turks, to Islam!
Give the treasury to the people,
Turgut Bey.
You'll gain the people's hearts.
And they'll hear that you took the castle.
The people will be ruled justly now.
Thank you, Osman Bey.
So, Osman Bey. İnegöl is next.
Nikola must be prepared.
It won't be easy to take İnegöl.
But we'll do it.
Share the treasury between the alps
and the people.
Alps will get their spoils!
And encouraged by the
spirit of conquest.
Alright.
The target is İnegöl now!
The antidote is working.
With Allah's help, you'll be
on your feet soon.
Thank you, master.
I owe you a life.
Alaca.
Can you give me water?
It's empty. I'll be back.
My enduring Cornelia.
Are you any better?
Thanks to you.
Alaca.
Come with me outside.
Now, listen to me carefully.
You'll keep your eyes
on Cornelia.
You'll inform me if you
see anything wrong.
What is it, Mother Selcan?
It's, my girl...
I don't believe that Zehra
would do this treachery.
Selcan still suspects me.
That old woman is too smart.
She might be a problem.
We'll make sure she can't
question you.
Barkın Bey's coins changed the
way of your heart.
You used your vote for him.
I have, my bey.
When the beys voted for him.
She is gossipping my bey
like crones.
No.
Not like that, Malhun Hatun.
Barkın Bey respects you.
The recent events affected him,
apparently.
My bey.
Hasan Bey speaks softly.
He is afraid to speak fully.
He can't openly say that Barkın Bey
was out of his way.
Everyone will be ruled as
they deserve.
Hasan Bey.
If you voted. You'll face
the consequences.
You are allowed to leave.
Hasan Bey voted Barkın Bey because
he had to.
He is one of us.
Protect him.
As you order, my bey.
Still, he didn't stand against him.
He voted for Barkın.
How did you come to
this conclusion, Osman?
To not create unrest.
Even the things he knows,
he speaks in his manners.
His situation puts him under shame.
That's how, Malhun.
You stay close to him.
Barkın must be sharpening his blade.
As you order, my bey.
İbrahim Fakih.
Who stepped into his shadow?
Who did he talk to?
He was talking closely with Barkın Bey.
They were together all the time.
Who else was there?
No one that is important, my bey.
What did he do after leaving?
Nothing suspicious on the road, my bey.
But...
we lost his trace near İnegöl.
İbrahim Fakih.
What are you after?
Enough to avoid the alps following you...
Go on.
You can leave.
Nothing happens out of our will.
In the west; lands, castles, even
cities...
change hands through marriages.
You will be the ruler of
the two tribes...
through a marriage,
just like a westerner.
Both İhvaz and Umur Bey wanted
a bey like me to rule their tribes.
May I enter, Barkın Bey?
Come, Hüsamettin.
Bad news, sir.
Say it!
Turgut Bey.
He took İnhisar.
He put his own flag there.
Turgut is mad.
He is rivaling Osman.
Turgut.
I won't let him ruin my plans
with his fury.
Even if he is Osman's enemy...
he'll choke in my darkness if he
messes with my plans.
Where does Barkın and İbrahim Fakih
know each other from?
He had Fakih perform the
marriage ceremony.
When I wasn't in the tribe, he gathered
a council to be a bey.
Who does your sickness help, Malhun?
To Barkın who wants to win without
anyone objecting to him.
Do you think it was him, my bey?
Is that so...
What about Selvi?
Selvi too?
We'll find out.
We'll find it all out.
Allah bless your hands, my wife.
It's delicious.
It feels like honey.
Here.
Enjoy it, Cerkutay.
Enjoy it, my husband.
Mashallah to my wife.
How she listens to her husband!
This is empty too, Cerkutay.
Do you want me to bring
another pot?
That soup won't satisfy me at all.
Cook meaty bulghur so that
we can satisfy our hunger.
Did you cook it before?
Mad girl knows her husband.
It's empty.
Yes, it is.
You have eaten everything in the tent,
Cerkutay!
If you are still hungry, go cook yourself!
I have things to do!
Clear the table as well!
How can you be so relentless
to your husband?
Can't you give me some food?
I told Mother Selcan that...
...a cup of honey wasn't enough!
We needed honey full of hive!
Now I suffer.
Oh, mad girl!
Harmankaya Castle.
I couldn't attend your feast, but...
Turgut Bey, I want to make an
agreement with you.
Have a seat please.
I should state that...
If you have your hand in the
death of Mari...
Talk Nicola...
So that I kill you.
Turgut Bey, why would I want to kill her?
Why would I wait so much to
kill her if I wanted her dead?
Turgut, please!
Will you calm down please?
If he played a role in Mari's death...
I wouldn't let him live.
Please.
Keep her name out of your mouth.
Never ever again.
Okay Turgut Bey.
Just listen what the agreement is about,
at least.
I offer to use Inegol and Harmankaya
bazaars collectively.
Both your lives and your goods will be
safe in Inegol Bazaar.
I assure you.
I want to make a written agreement...
...so you have no doubt in your mind.
Here.
Common usage of the bazaars will benefit
both sides.
Once we provide the security...
...all the merchants around the world
will rush into our bazaar.
If you accept my conditions, all of those
will happen, Kossess.
If you abide by my conditions.
Inegol Bazaar is a great opportunity
for you, Turgut Bey.
Especially at these times when
Turks are poor.
At this way, Turkmens will not have to
rely on Osman who only thinks of himself.
Right?
A Bey should seek for opportunities.
Right, Barkın?
So, my Bey...
They acted when I was sick...
...and you were away.
Like there was no other time.
I act when you are absent, sister.
Should I have gotten you up from
your sick bed?
Selvi Hatun is right.
But if Barkın Bey invited only the Beys
who would vote for him...
...I can change my mind then.
I didn't invite anyone.
I just attended.
They thought I was suitable
for the Bey position.
And I didn't refuse it.
He gave away gold to Beys beforehand.
He deceived them.
Is this right, Ibrahim Fakih?
It was Umur Bey's gold.
It's his bequest.
He told me to share it to
his family and Beys.
There's your share too.
There's no question that
I can't answer.
But if you are to ask questions...
you have to ask it to Turgut.
You are right, Barkin.
You do things without us.
But you stand behind us.
That Turgut Bey...
He went too far.
Now he will claim the castle
and gain strength.
He'll face us some day.
I'll cut him down before
he grows too much.
Regulation requires this, Osman Bey.
Having two leaders is not appropriate.
You are right.
You are right Ibrahim Fakih.
You heal us with your hand
and your words.
May Allah bless you, Ibrahim Fakih.
You healed my sheikh.
I am just an occasion.
Heal comes from Allah.
So, what do you want in return, Nikola?
You'll give Inhisar to me.
I will pay you tax.
Turgut Bey.
A Turk cannot be imprisoned in
a stone castle.
Only Turgut can make this decision.
That Turgut Bey...
From whom he gains his glory?
He faces all those Lords and Emperor
with his tiny tribe.
He must have an ally.
Kossess killed my brother.
And Nikola is chasing a chance to
backstab us.
Maybe they are working together.
The others are our nemesis'
We were together for politics.
But that Turgut...
He backstabbed me.
He joined the enemy...
...he conquered Inhisar castle, where
I have been yearning for.
What is your plan Osman Bey?
I am always with you, as the leader
of two huge tribes.
Eyvallah Barkin.
My move is obvious.
I will take Inhisar castle back
from Turgut Bey.
I'll claim his tribe.
I will exile him from these lands
with no horse or sandals!
Traitors must pay.
However...
Before this...
I will brighten the suspicious death
of Umur Bey.
Whoever did this...
I will shed their blood in sterams!
They have been cruel.
They are going to be perished.
They have already been, my Bey.
I killed Mongols with my hands.
I am not talking about that, Barkın.
I am not talking about that.
Osman!
- Osman!
- Mother?
Osman! Osman!
Osman!
- Mother!
Mother!
Who did tihs?
Who did this?
Who?
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com